https://www.cardquest.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
JavaScript seems to be disabled in your browser.
You must have JavaScript enabled in your browser to utilize the functionality of this website.
Card Quest - Your Key To Access Control
My Cart:
0 item(s) - $0.00
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Se Habla Español
Search:
Search
COVID-19 ProductsID Card FormatsAccess ControlAccess Control SystemsProdatakeyTwo Door KitPro Wireless - 1 to 1000 DoorsPower Supplies & BatteriesKeriTwo Door KitPower Supplies & BatteriesOne and Two Door SystemsCard ReadersSchlage (Allegion)HIDProximityiClassiClass SEOmnikeyID Cards | Fobs | TagsProximity CardsHIDIdentivSchlage (Allegion)IndalaAWIDKeriKantechBoschCasi-RuscoSecuraKeyProximity Key Fobs & TagsHIDIdentivSchlage (Allegion)IndalaAWIDKeriKantechBoschCasi-RuscoiClass Cards, Key Fobs & TagsMIFARE CardsHIDSchlage (Allegion)PVC CardsWhiteMagnetic StripeAdhesive BackColorHIDIdentivSchlage (Allegion)IndalaAWIDKeriKantechBoschEvolisCasi-RuscoSecuraKeySurveillanceIP CamerasDahuaIndoorOutdoorPan Tilt Zoom (PTZ)SamsungFLIRGanzPelcoHikvisionAnalog CamerasPan Tilt Zoom (PTZ)SamsungVideo RecordersNetwork Video Recorders (NVR)Digital Video Recorders (DVR)Video Surveillance MonitorsNetwork SwitchesPower Over Ethernet (PoE)Non-Power Over EthernetPower Supplies & BatteriesSurveillance AccessoriesDecodersEncodersAdaptersNetwork ControllersAnalog ControllersNetwork SoftwareLensesCamera HousingCamera MountsRepeaters & ConvertersUTP DevicesPower SuppliesAccess ControlSurveillanceID Cards | Fobs | TagsProximity CardsHIDIdentivSchlage (Allegion)IndalaAWIDKeriKantechBoschCasi-RuscoSecuraKeyProximity Key Fobs & TagsHIDIdentivSchlage (Allegion)IndalaAWIDKeriKantechBoschCasi-RuscoiClass Cards, Key Fobs & TagsMIFARE CardsHID MifareSchlage (Allegion)PVC CardsWhiteMagnetic StripeAdhesive BackColorHIDIdentivSchlage (Allegion)IndalaAWIDKeriKantechBoschEvolisCasi-RuscoSecuraKeyCard PrintersSingle SidedDual SidedLaminatingRetransferPrinter BundlesFargoMagicardEvolisNiscaZebraDatacardDiscontinued PrintersSwiftColor IDPPrinter SuppliesColor RibbonsMono RibbonsCleaning KitsLaminatesRetransfer FilmInkjet CartridgesFargo SuppliesMagicard SuppliesEvolis SuppliesNisca SuppliesZebra SuppliesDatacard SuppliesIDP SuppliesDiscontinued Printer SuppliesID SoftwareAsure ID Software (HID)CardExchange SoftwareIWS SoftwareJolly SoftwareCard Studio Software (Zebra)Photo ID CamerasLanyardsStandard LanyardsBreakaway LanyardsCustom LanyardsOpen Ended LanyardsBadge ReelsStandard Badge ReelsBadge HoldersMost Popular Badge HoldersBadge BuddiesCardProtectorsColor HoldersFlexible HoldersProx Card HoldersRigid HoldersWallet HoldersMagnetic HoldersArm Band HoldersWristband ID HoldersName Tag HoldersBadge ClipsStrap ClipsAdhesive Clips & PinsPlastic AttachmentsMagnetic AttachmentsVisitor BadgesExpiring Visitor BadgesNon-Expiring Visitor BadgesVisitor Management SoftwareVisitor Management Printers & ScannersReusable Badge BackersParking PermitsBinders | Clipboards | Security TapeID AccessoriesMetal Badge RacksSlot PunchesWireless NetworkingMonthly GiveawayTraining & Information
Categories
COVID-19 ProductsID Card FormatsAccess ControlAccess Control SystemsProdatakeyTwo Door KitPro Wireless - 1 to 1000 DoorsPower Supplies & BatteriesKeriTwo Door KitPower Supplies & BatteriesOne and Two Door SystemsCard ReadersSchlage (Allegion)HIDProximityiClassiClass SEOmnikeyID Cards | Fobs | TagsProximity CardsHIDIdentivSchlage (Allegion)IndalaAWIDKeriKantechBoschCasi-RuscoSecuraKeyProximity Key Fobs & TagsHIDIdentivSchlage (Allegion)IndalaAWIDKeriKantechBoschCasi-RuscoiClass Cards, Key Fobs & TagsMIFARE CardsHIDSchlage (Allegion)PVC CardsWhiteMagnetic StripeAdhesive BackColorHIDIdentivSchlage (Allegion)IndalaAWIDKeriKantechBoschEvolisCasi-RuscoSecuraKeySurveillanceIP CamerasDahuaIndoorOutdoorPan Tilt Zoom (PTZ)SamsungFLIRGanzPelcoHikvisionAnalog CamerasPan Tilt Zoom (PTZ)SamsungVideo RecordersNetwork Video Recorders (NVR)Digital Video Recorders (DVR)Video Surveillance MonitorsNetwork SwitchesPower Over Ethernet (PoE)Non-Power Over EthernetPower Supplies & BatteriesSurveillance AccessoriesDecodersEncodersAdaptersNetwork ControllersAnalog ControllersNetwork SoftwareLensesCamera HousingCamera MountsRepeaters & ConvertersUTP DevicesPower SuppliesAccess ControlSurveillanceID Cards | Fobs | TagsProximity CardsHIDIdentivSchlage (Allegion)IndalaAWIDKeriKantechBoschCasi-RuscoSecuraKeyProximity Key Fobs & TagsHIDIdentivSchlage (Allegion)IndalaAWIDKeriKantechBoschCasi-RuscoiClass Cards, Key Fobs & TagsMIFARE CardsHID MifareSchlage (Allegion)PVC CardsWhiteMagnetic StripeAdhesive BackColorHIDIdentivSchlage (Allegion)IndalaAWIDKeriKantechBoschEvolisCasi-RuscoSecuraKeyCard PrintersSingle SidedDual SidedLaminatingRetransferPrinter BundlesFargoMagicardEvolisNiscaZebraDatacardDiscontinued PrintersSwiftColor IDPPrinter SuppliesColor RibbonsMono RibbonsCleaning KitsLaminatesRetransfer FilmInkjet CartridgesFargo SuppliesMagicard SuppliesEvolis SuppliesNisca SuppliesZebra SuppliesDatacard SuppliesIDP SuppliesDiscontinued Printer SuppliesID SoftwareAsure ID Software (HID)CardExchange SoftwareIWS SoftwareJolly SoftwareCard Studio Software (Zebra)Photo ID CamerasLanyardsStandard LanyardsBreakaway LanyardsCustom LanyardsOpen Ended LanyardsBadge ReelsStandard Badge ReelsBadge HoldersMost Popular Badge HoldersBadge BuddiesCardProtectorsColor HoldersFlexible HoldersProx Card HoldersRigid HoldersWallet HoldersMagnetic HoldersArm Band HoldersWristband ID HoldersName Tag HoldersBadge ClipsStrap ClipsAdhesive Clips & PinsPlastic AttachmentsMagnetic AttachmentsVisitor BadgesExpiring Visitor BadgesNon-Expiring Visitor BadgesVisitor Management SoftwareVisitor Management Printers & ScannersReusable Badge BackersParking PermitsBinders | Clipboards | Security TapeID AccessoriesMetal Badge RacksSlot PunchesWireless NetworkingMonthly GiveawayTraining & Information
Home
>
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Card Quest collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the www.cardquest.com website. This privacy policy applies to the website and all products and services offered by Card Quest.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when users visit our site, register on the website, place an order, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our website. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. Users may, however, visit our website anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about users whenever they interact with our website. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about users means of connection to our website, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance user experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the website may not function properly.
How we use collected information
Card Quest may collect and use users personal information for the following purposes:
·      To improve customer service
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
·      To personalize user experience
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
·      To improve our website
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
·      To process payments
We may use the information users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
·      To run a promotion, contest, survey or other website feature
To send users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
·      To send periodic emails
We may use the email address to send user information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the website or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out emails, newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our website that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website. In addition, these websites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These websites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our website, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
Card Quest has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We will post a notification on the privacy policy page (this page) of our website. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. This is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this website, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our website. Your continued use of the website following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at:
Address:
Card Quest
PO Box 1915
Elfers, FL 33680
Phone:  (888) 240-3738
Email: sales@cardquest.com
Website: www.cardquest.com
Categories
COVID-19 ProductsID Card FormatsAccess ControlAccess Control SystemsProdatakeyTwo Door KitPro Wireless - 1 to 1000 DoorsPower Supplies & BatteriesKeriTwo Door KitPower Supplies & BatteriesOne and Two Door SystemsCard ReadersSchlage (Allegion)HIDProximityiClassiClass SEOmnikeyID Cards | Fobs | TagsProximity CardsHIDIdentivSchlage (Allegion)IndalaAWIDKeriKantechBoschCasi-RuscoSecuraKeyProximity Key Fobs & TagsHIDIdentivSchlage (Allegion)IndalaAWIDKeriKantechBoschCasi-RuscoiClass Cards, Key Fobs & TagsMIFARE CardsHIDSchlage (Allegion)PVC CardsWhiteMagnetic StripeAdhesive BackColorHIDIdentivSchlage (Allegion)IndalaAWIDKeriKantechBoschEvolisCasi-RuscoSecuraKeySurveillanceIP CamerasDahuaIndoorOutdoorPan Tilt Zoom (PTZ)SamsungFLIRGanzPelcoHikvisionAnalog CamerasPan Tilt Zoom (PTZ)SamsungVideo RecordersNetwork Video Recorders (NVR)Digital Video Recorders (DVR)Video Surveillance MonitorsNetwork SwitchesPower Over Ethernet (PoE)Non-Power Over EthernetPower Supplies & BatteriesSurveillance AccessoriesDecodersEncodersAdaptersNetwork ControllersAnalog ControllersNetwork SoftwareLensesCamera HousingCamera MountsRepeaters & ConvertersUTP DevicesPower SuppliesAccess ControlSurveillanceID Cards | Fobs | TagsProximity CardsHIDIdentivSchlage (Allegion)IndalaAWIDKeriKantechBoschCasi-RuscoSecuraKeyProximity Key Fobs & TagsHIDIdentivSchlage (Allegion)IndalaAWIDKeriKantechBoschCasi-RuscoiClass Cards, Key Fobs & TagsMIFARE CardsHID MifareSchlage (Allegion)PVC CardsWhiteMagnetic StripeAdhesive BackColorHIDIdentivSchlage (Allegion)IndalaAWIDKeriKantechBoschEvolisCasi-RuscoSecuraKeyCard PrintersSingle SidedDual SidedLaminatingRetransferPrinter BundlesFargoMagicardEvolisNiscaZebraDatacardDiscontinued PrintersSwiftColor IDPPrinter SuppliesColor RibbonsMono RibbonsCleaning KitsLaminatesRetransfer FilmInkjet CartridgesFargo SuppliesMagicard SuppliesEvolis SuppliesNisca SuppliesZebra SuppliesDatacard SuppliesIDP SuppliesDiscontinued Printer SuppliesID SoftwareAsure ID Software (HID)CardExchange SoftwareIWS SoftwareJolly SoftwareCard Studio Software (Zebra)Photo ID CamerasLanyardsStandard LanyardsBreakaway LanyardsCustom LanyardsOpen Ended LanyardsBadge ReelsStandard Badge ReelsBadge HoldersMost Popular Badge HoldersBadge BuddiesCardProtectorsColor HoldersFlexible HoldersProx Card HoldersRigid HoldersWallet HoldersMagnetic HoldersArm Band HoldersWristband ID HoldersName Tag HoldersBadge ClipsStrap ClipsAdhesive Clips & PinsPlastic AttachmentsMagnetic AttachmentsVisitor BadgesExpiring Visitor BadgesNon-Expiring Visitor BadgesVisitor Management SoftwareVisitor Management Printers & ScannersReusable Badge BackersParking PermitsBinders | Clipboards | Security TapeID AccessoriesMetal Badge RacksSlot PunchesWireless NetworkingMonthly GiveawayTraining & Information
My Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Compare Products
You have no items to compare.
FREE GROUND SHIPPING ON ORDERS $100 OR MORE.Only valid within the Continental U.S.
Card Quest, Inc.
All Rights Reserved
Comodo SSL
